HARDEEP KUMAR

Front End Web Developer

 $$$ $$ https://github.com/hk1728557 \otimes hk1728557@gmail.com $$ +91-7779978231 $$ https://www.linkedin.com/in/hardeep-k/link$

SUMMARY

I am Hardeep Kumar, a skilled WordPress, Web developer with experience in building interactive user interfaces and efficient Web applications And Figma Designer. Master's in Computer Application and a solid academic background, I am committed to continuously expanding my skills and delivering exceptional results in every project.

SKILLS

Computer Languages : HTML, CSS, javaScript Web Technologies : WordPress, Reactjs,

App Development : FlutterFlow

Designing Tools : Figma

EXPERIENCES

Frontend Developer Intern Future Core Innovations Jun 2024 - Present

- Developed the product from scratch.
- used reusable widgets and made UI for 15+ Screens.
- used responsive widgets for web and mobile Screens.
- API Integration and Error Handling.

Figma Designer, WordPress and FrontEnd FlutterFlow Developer $\ Sep\ 2022$ - $\ Jan\ 2024$ ELUNICO IT Solution

- web Applications And mobile Applications made UI screens in Using FlutterFlow
- Developed the product from scratch.
- used reusable widgets and made UI for 20+ Screens.
- Web Screens and mobile Screen Figma Design

Frontend Developer Intern CloudSoft Technology April 2022 - Sep 2022

- Developed the product from scratch.
- Used reusable widgets and made UI for 11+ screens.
- Integrated authentication and Firestore services using Firebase.

PROJECTS

https://calcuttapoliceclub.in/

• website developed in wordpress

https://infactoai.in/

• website developed in wordpress

NewsApp for web

- A News App using API from newsapi.org
- Used Bloc state management technique.

Chat App

- Implemented Login and Sign Up authentication using Firebase.
- Used Firestore for messaging services.

JsonDataPlayList, Flutter, Json File

- Read Local Json File.
- use flutter packages and display UI

House Price Predictor App, MongoDb, Flutter, Flask, Scrapy

- Scraped 11000+ house data from magicbricks and stored them in a MySQL Database. Built the Regression model after Data Cleaning.
- Created a Flutter app that gets the price from Flask API and Regression Model.

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION

• Master in Computer Application Vinoba Bhave Univesity, Hazaribag Jharkhand sep 2020 - 2022

2015 - 2018

• Bachelor in Computer Science St. Columba's College, Vinoba Bhave University, Hazaribag Jharkhand

CERTIFICATES

- Jons Hopkins University HTML, CSS, and JavaScript for web developer
- Coursera(Google)
 Basic to Advance Python
- Google Digital Garage The Fundamental of Digital Marketing